hello my name is green and welcome back
to another episode of hermitcraft we
have been very very busy and i think
before i even get into anything i want
to show you the time lapse because
something weird happened what
was that enderman anyway so something
weird happened and yes this bit
joe's up there what's going on what's he
looking at i don't know what's going on
well anyway so basically we had a little
team meeting between everyone and
they're about to fire fire what there's
a cease-fire you can't you can't be
firing anything is it from there is that
is that it so that's their base over
there and as you can see
they have made some big progress and it
looks like they've got two bases now
which is super weird oh
oh no this doesn't look good does it
this doesn't look good so we had a team
meeting and we started delegating all of
the jobs and me and iskall straight
after the meeting we were like really
pumped about building our base
so we did and we built a lot but i'm not
going to show you that there because i'm
going to show you that in a time lapse
right now oh goodness they've put
coordinates in the chat i think they i
think they're taking aim
they shouldn't be firing anything at us
oh my goodness this is scary well we'll
find out after the time lapse what
happens all right so as you know we had
that one bit on the side and it was
looking kind of lonely on its own so we
went a little bit overboard this really
wasn't planned i took a picture again a
screenshot and then i drew very badly
and i just drew these like circular
shapes and the idea is that it's meant
to look like a futuristic bunker you can
kind of see it's got that old-fashioned
bunker style with the
very small slit in the middle and then
it's sort of wrapped around by this
white concrete so it's meant to
represent what an old bunker looks like
but taken into
the 22nd century style or this sort of
futuristic style that we're going for i
think it works really well but in
reality in minecraft all of these
materials are really not that resistant
so terracotta and glass are two of the
materials that are the easiest to remove
or destroy with tnt so if they manage to
get the creepers on our base
it can do some really really big damage
so there's something to consider there
but we are going to be putting in some
pretty heavy defenses to try and
mitigate any damage
and as you can see we kind of played
around with a little tower on the left
there but for the most part that is the
front of the building and you can see
that there's a little g in the top right
hand corner you know g team
so let's go back and see what they're up
to hey doc get get get get out
doc
what's doc looking at he's looking
directly in the air like there's
something there i see nothing
oh oh wait
[Music]
okay i
um i understand now
there is a flying cow they have
catapulted a cow
all the way over to our base
except they missed well there it is
yeah
what
[Laughter]
okay so they're practicing their missile
launching and i anyway i should give you
a tour of the base
oh that thing is that that thing is
going to be deadly obviously they're not
going to be sending over cows that's
just like the test dummy they're gonna
be sending over creepers
oh no we need to prepare at least we
know what's going to be coming for us
anyway let me give you a quick tour of
our base
so this is the g team headquarters
and it's still not finished it's not
finished at all but i've got to show you
around because there's been so much
progress in one session alone me and
iskal spent about four hours
making this whole thing just because we
got super inspired i've got to admit it
looks really cool so this bit here is no
longer the focus it's just one side of
the build and i'll be honest this wasn't
really planned so let's go and have a
look this is the main part and this is
now the front door there's still a lot
to go on so this bit over here this is
going to be like the landscaping and
it's going to have loads of these like
layers all the way around but stress
monster has been delegated that job so
i'm hoping that she'll put that together
fairly soon tango has been delegated
redstone defense obviously as he is the
biggest redstoner on our team and this
is going to be the control room for all
of that so we've got a great view
directly opposite their base and we'll
have all the buttons we need to press
all the traps and mechanisms and
defenses etc etc as you can see there's
not a lot of
interior going on there's barely a floor
to walk on
this is uh iskal's little baby over here
he decided that he really wanted an
aquarium here so we now have a g team
aquarium i think the plan is to put a
couple of dolphins in here as well but
look at this there's loads of fish it
goes all the way down it's really cool
like that is a really nice feature we
really want this base to look good
there's unfortunately not a lot in here
but what cleo was doing was working on a
meeting room table which is right here
so this is our meeting room right uh
where we've got all this open glass and
the open back it looks really cool and
she's even made these cool chairs with
pigs upside down and we can all have a
brilliant meeting like this how awesome
is the cake and cookies i mean look how
awesome our team is cake and cookies you
can't beat this so that's our little
meeting room and you can see that just
look how much this is coming together
this is a real team effort and not to
mention the fact that a few team members
have been collecting resources like
crazy
crazy amounts of resources so that's the
main base and it's got this little tower
on the top with a few like antenna and i
do want to work a little bit on this a
little later on as well but i think
we need to do something about our
mustache friend as you know the teams
are really starting to shape up and
mumbo isn't on a side so i'm thinking
we go and ask him to not be on our side
let's go and get this gal and see if we
can meet up with him what's up with your
face dude look he came to my base the
other day
oh
it's actually is
really horrible dude they're my eyes
this is uh
oh yeah this is bum bumper fight the
skull face
this is the worst thing i've ever seen
in my life man
that is oh come on is that it's not nice
thing you've ever seen
it's the worst thing i've ever seen in
my life oh you must have you mustn't
have you mustn't have had a mirror when
they took away your mustache dude
oh yeah okay fine okay
yeah i think i think we shouldn't swap
mustaches around i think
it should stay where it is iska has the
beard i'm clean shaven and mumba has the
mustache when we start mixing and
matching it doesn't work
it does not yeah it doesn't it doesn't
agree
anyway i've called together this little
meeting because we need to we need to
get mumbo in on what's going on on the
server iskall he's kind of like been off
to the side for uh the whole trip
chilling just not not
where have you been dude like let me
know i've been i've been chilling out uh
and i've been just doing my thing
being incredibly neutral
and trying to stay out of or
what we're talking about
i mean do you even do you even know
what's been going on do you know like
all the pranks have you got any idea
look okay look all right i mean
okay right take a seat
sit sit down you need to sit down for
this
this is probably for the better yep so i
don't know if you've noticed mumbo but
there's a war going on
so at the moment the server has pretty
much split down the middle and there's a
team of five on one side and there's a
team of
six on the other i think or maybe it's
four or five i don't know but there's
now two teams the g team which me and
iscal are on and
g team because we've all got g's in our
name you see yeah and
yep
the other team which is called star i
can't remember what it stands for it's
super silly super
super terrible off to the best of the
stars
but yeah
so anyway
we want to get you in because i've been
reading my comments i've been eyeing up
the reddit and all sorts and everyone
thinks that you should join the g team
and we're
we're here to ask you
not to join the g team
no no don't look sad we need you to
infiltrate the other team and be our
mole we need to know what's going on we
might need some sabotage in there
so
we think that they're going to try and
recruit you just like we are now but
we're telling you to take take them up
on their offer
you got it okay so
you want me
to not join you
and
join the other team
but join
you you got it you
information is this because i don't have
a g in my no no you're mumbo gumbo i
mean don't don't yeah let's not even
pretend that you're that you haven't got
a g in your name you are part of the g
team and you are mumbo jumbo that might
give me away
well you can pretend that you're mumbo
jumbo for now but your mumbo gumbo when
you're talking to us all right yeah yeah
but here's the thing got it got it got
it so here's this is where it gets a
little bit complicated the audience
watching this right now
we'll all go and tell the star team that
you're a mole straight away we all know
that and they might even see this video
themselves so we know that they know
that you are a mole and that we know
you're a mole
right are you with me right because they
know that you're a mole exactly so you
need to tell them immediately that you
are a mole and you're gonna work for
them against us
double agent straight off from the back
double mole double mole
double mod moldo gumbo
so well i don't know when they might do
it but you know we've got at least
another week of base building have you
seen the bases it looks pretty cool yeah
yeah yeah i've seen them they look
pretty they look pretty insane
so i think we've got another like we've
got another few days at least of
building i don't know exactly when the
ceasefire flag is coming down
but i'm absolutely sure that they're
going to do a recruitment drive because
they're i think they're a player short
of our team like in terms of raw numbers
so
they're probably going to stay
approachable yeah like hang around their
base like almost walk this street
walk the streets
you know
make sure you fix your mustache every
morning
yeah brush your mustache
fix your tie
what do you say though mumbo gum i like
the sound of this this seems like uh it
seems like a good move and of course
this meeting never happened no no no no
of course well i'm gonna go i'm gonna
head off and do some mold duties then
i'll get right to it you know i'm a hard
working guy you gotta wait until they
ask you to join the team you can't just
walk into their base and be like hey
guys i'm a mole you gotta wait you gotta
wait for them to ask you to be on the
team
right yeah yeah yeah oh maybe this is a
bad idea is gal this is a bad idea
immediately he's just gonna walk in and
tell him already i'm just panicking
inside
right
do you think do you think i could grow
this without knowing a little a little
about things hey
this is going to end badly so mumbo is
now officially the g team mole and that
is absolutely perfect i actually heard
doc and some of the other guys talking
about trying to recruit mumbo so i'm
getting in there early to make sure that
he doesn't end up
on their team without like without me
and a skeleton is here like
hey mumbo
help us out and while i'm at it actually
i should go and pick up all of the tnt
because
in typical concord fashion cub fan has
created top gun powder which is
basically well yeah tnt
fire charges
all of the stuff you would need to wreck
a base
and he's cashing in big time so i'm
thinking we
cash in and take
the boom boom boom boxes we take all of
it
yep they're all gone
doc's beating me to it doc's big creeper
missile thing takes lots of tnt to fire
and he's clearly bought up all of the
stock what about the fire charges yes
okay so
we can take all of this
now i actually already have a lot of the
materials needed to make lots of tnt
however i want to make sure that i keep
this completely depleted so that the
other team
can't keep stocking up so easily
okay so i've soaked up all of the fire
charges but this tnt thing is not good i
need me some boom boom boxes well i
don't need me some boom boom boxes what
i need is to make sure the other team
can't get lots of tnt
so i'll just ask cub hmm i can make a
special order for you now that sounds
like
he could do that for doc as well
but if doc's like getting lots of tnt
together
i should probably get lots of tnt
together as well hello green hello hello
all right so um i've pretty much uh
taken all the fire charges uh at the
moment
uh wow you've obviously seen the
fight going on and you're cashing in big
time so oh yeah oh yeah uh you're out of
tnt and i kind of want to make sure that
the other guys don't get too much tnt
okay okay um yeah let's see so how much
how much are you thinking you might need
how many how many stacks of tnt i
because i mean at concord i mean we got
pretty much an unlimited supply so i
mean if you want to make a big order i
mean we'd be more than happy to
accommodate that you know maybe give you
a little bit of a discount if you order
more
okay okay well i don't think you can
ever really have enough you know what i
mean uh how much will
that get me uh two stacks of diamonds
uh i'd say that gives you about a
hundred stacks of tnt yeah one in a bit
for a stack of tnt okay all right
i'll take it i'll take it i'll take it i
hope you're not giving the other guys
such a sweet discount you know well i i
i can neither confirm nor deny this i
cannot discuss internal workings of
concorp nor any deals we may or may not
have made a businessman over here
cashing in cashing in on
this so i'm gonna leave you to it i'll
i'll deliver this tnt probably within
the next two days sweet make sure that
they can't see it you know you gotta
this you know discreet delivery
do you have a like a like a vault of
some place so that i can like put it in
like so that's super secure that i can't
get to it yeah i tell you what i'm going
to create a little delivery hole so that
you can safely and securely
give us the the goods without them
knowing you know
gotcha gotcha that sounds great man that
sounds great okay i can't help but feel
i'm getting massively conned but what do
you expect when you do dealings with the
con corp
i already paid oh no this is totally
legit man this is totally legit it's
gonna be gonna be great i'm happy to do
business with you my friend
thanks kev there's obviously still quite
a lot to do when it comes to the g-team
base however i'm really enjoying it i
mean you can obviously tell because i
built for like four hours straight with
iskall so that's two people so that
would have been eight hours on my own
but the whole point of this is that it's
really fun to build and i know it's
probably going to take some damage but
it's honestly just had me really
enthused i haven't built in like this in
a really long time i do like my base
over there and i know that i'm i'm even
using exactly the same block palette for
this base but sometimes it's nice just
to work on a different project
especially if it moves very very quickly
now i think that the interior is
something i'm definitely going to leave
till later on oh and i also just
finished that little area for cubs so
hold on who's online
impulse and curb his impulse around
doesn't look like it when cub fan
delivers the tnt all he's got to do and
i've told him this is he puts a lever
here
right clicks and it opens up to some
chests where he's going to put the stuff
when he's done he removes the leafer and
he puts a flower right here to show that
it's been delivered or a long grass or
some kind of plant that won't look out
of place there that way we've got a
secret delivery system that no one else
can interrupt especially the other team
and it's kind of like you know by the
front so it's like a proper delivery
system
as for the back of this building there's
still a lot to do like this whole chunk
here and i'm kind of thinking i'm
gonna replicate what i've got but
i'm not entirely sure yet i do think it
looks cool this whole thing i i don't
want to make it too complicated here but
i am going to finish this tower at the
end of the day the back of this base
isn't really going to be seen that much
nor is it the focus of everything so i
think it's just got to look nice but
without distracting or detracting from
the front i think each layer needs to be
a bit thicker but it's something that
will develop over time you also see here
that i've created these like whole this
hole here now this i'm hoping will be a
chandelier that goes through multiple
layers kind of like in my base so this
would dangle down and stop about here
and it would be a chandelier in the big
hall here and this is going to light
things up so this is like the main hall
even though the entrance is going to be
over there so you enter through there
you go into that hall i guess which is
like the lobby and then you come here
which is the main lobby
i don't there's too many lobbies here
and there's other plans as well so down
here this is where we've been like
storing all of our stuff this is mainly
my shocker boxes
and we've been working down here
so fortunately
there's this little ravine directly
under our base
and we've been opening it up to create a
bunch of space because
part of the build is going to be down
here and i thought what a brilliant
place to make this
in a ravine now obviously it needs a lot
of tidying up like
it doesn't really feel like a ravine at
the moment because it kind of etches in
too much and it's a bit messy over here
for example it shouldn't be too
difficult to fix but
it is really really cool i'm not gonna
lie and what we're gonna make here
should be really interesting as well
and then of course we're gonna have all
of our secrets and i'm counting on you
guys watching the video
not to tell everyone where all of our
secrets are because we should let them
find out for themselves that's the best
way to do this and through the power of
editing there is a wall right there that
was previously completely open and
that's because there's actually been
another day gone by and i have been
still building this base i am so sorry
if you're expecting more like work on my
other base over there i will do some
probably in the next episode but this is
now complete i've actually finished off
this side and even added some bits at
the bottom and i'm really happy with how
this looks i for some reason when i
start a project i really really have to
finish it so i'm pretty happy with how
this has come out and i'm wondering if
cub has delivered anything no flour no
delivery but i tell you what we did add
yesterday me me and iskal or iskal and i
we added a doorbell and this is just a
little joke that we've added here so
this is obviously the front door but
it's not the real front door to the base
we added a doorbell and if you click it
this is what happens
[Music]
she's not clocked me but she's meant to
throw a potion it's
there we go thanks gertrude
he hit the doorbell
you hit the doorbell it opens up it it
fires a piece of paper at you that has a
chance i actually got really lucky here
it says you sir are a poop
there's actually many options for this
but this one is um there's only six of
these so there's a go away you sir are a
poop and you're not welcome here
so we put that in together and uh this
guy's actually just logged on but we
showed this in his video as well it's
pretty funny so
hit the doorbell in comes gertrude she
says go away she may or may not throw a
potion at you and then she scarpers back
again
oh i love this thing so much
please don't kill me oh
let's go
what are you doing
this is just it was me
he might have thought that was someone
else
so i'm afraid that's all i have time for
for today building all of this took up
like an entire day just of building like
eight nine hours solid in total out of
everything and then that's not even
including the normal recording time so
the time lapses alone took a really
really long time
so i think next episode i want to work a
little bit on my base back there but i
also want to start kitting out this but
this was a totally necessary thing to do
we had to get the main shell of the base
ready so that we can actually start
filling it up
with all of the redstone needs and stuff
and it gives somewhere for tango to do
his magic
okay so that's it for me everyone thank
you very much for watching i hope you
enjoyed this video and good bye